(Rain pattering)
I'm afraid you have to decide right now
if you want to be registered
as a homosexual or a heterosexual.
I think I should be registered
as a heterosexual.
OK, I would like you to write your name
clearly on this form in capital letters.
"Thank God they wear those
waterproof ponchos," he thought.
- Yes, a lobster.
- Why a lobster?
Because lobsters live
for over 100 years,
I water-ski and swim quite well,
since I was a teenager.
A lobster is an excellent choice.
Later on he would learn
that she often got nosebleeds.
He thanked the waiter
who served him his coffee,
A woman who seemed to like
butter biscuits
who he would later find out
was absolutely heartless.
who was better at math than she was.
My mother entered the hotel but didn't
make it and was turned into a wolf.
One day,
I decided to enter the enclosure
which is also my defining characteristic.
My defining characteristic
is that I have a very beautiful smile.
She's the best hunter in the hotel,
silent and very fast.
One way is to rinse the clothes
with cold water then rub with sea salt.
The third way is to mix flour and water
into a paste, like toothpaste,
But just never use warm water
on blood, ever.
Well, let me know when
you feel better and we can dance again.
(Coughs and splutters.)
How many darts did you use yesterday?
(Coughs and splutters)
- This is not necessary.
- Please place your hand in the toaster.
What they do,
as soon as you enter the room,
My uncle used to know a waiter
who worked there.
No waiters know about the procedure,
which has become soft
due to the water and the soap.
Afterwards, they remove the heart,
the eyes and other vital organs of the body
Afterwards they throw
the remaining body parts
- New guests arrived yesterday.
- Yes, I saw.
WOMAN: One night on the coach, he sat next
to the woman who liked butter biscuits.
I'd give anything to go for a walk
with you and Bob one afternoon.
Some excuses are without doubt
better than others.
I always swallow after fellatio and I've
got absolutely no problem with anal sex
480, that would be even better.
A lobster.
As for you, they'll catch you and put you
in a pot of boiling water until you die.
Do you like to swim breaststroke,
front crawl, butterfly or backstroke?
If you encounter any problems,
any tensions, any arguing,
(Sounds of birdsong and running water)
for example,
read a work of classic literature
or to have sexual intercourse
with another person,
Well, I'll call you a little bit later,
after you've finished your shower.
We'll talk later.
We'll talk some other time
when it's quieter.
Well, I'll call you a little bit later,
after you've finished your shower.
We'll talk later.
(Coughs and splutters)
(Spluttering continues)
- Thank you.
- This is our new daughter.
Turn the light on please,
so I can see you better.
Doesn't matter.
These aren't tears, it's just water.
I just washed my face.
that is called the Red Intercourse.
I woke up terrified.
(Laughter)
- Better?
- Yes.
Much better.
My daughter says me
it's a very fine company.
That part about holiday destinations
in the Mediterranean was brilliant.
or red watercolour paint
or something like that.
Who will be able to live
on their own better?
You'd better get out while you still can.
As soon as his last patient left,
I entered his office and I said to him,
That story sounds really interesting
but I have to leave.
I just remembered I left some batteries
next to a tree down there.
Catching a rabbit is difficult,
but I'll try to do better.
Serifos: Greek island located
in the western Cyclades."
If it's better to see clearly
or to be short-sighted? Is that it?
There's no point in lying to you,
you'll find out sooner or later.
Good afternoon.
I can't go much faster.
Can I have a knife and fork, please?
Not a butter knife, a steak knife.